ATHUL J R

STUDENT FREELANCER AND



7560914142



athulkarthiK20@gmail.com



KOLLAM KERALA

I am Athul J R,a student with a passion for digital world and social wellbeing. This resume serves as a window into my journey, showcasing my academic and extracurricular accomplishments, as well as my personal and professional growth over the years. As a student, I have dedicated myself to acquiring knowledge, developing critical skills, and actively engaging in various projects and experiences. This portfolio is a testament to my commitment to excellence, and it has been created with the following objectives in mind:

EXPERIENCE

APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

ICFOSS

2020-present

WEB CONTENT MANAGER KERALA INFORMATION CENTER 2021-2022

- Database administration and website design
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that
- Conference management system for publication.
- Database administration and website design
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that
- Educational institutions and online Faculty management in kerala university.

EDUCATION

BSC COMPUTER SCIENCE

kerala university 2020-2023

CGPA-7.77

HIGHER SECONDARY

board of higher secondary education State board kerala 2018-2020

PERCENTAGE-96%

SECONDARY SCHOOL

2015-2016

PERCENTAGE-90%

EXPERTISE

- Web Design
- · Design Thinking
- Wireframe Creation
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy

- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication
- Creative & Professional

COURSE CERTIFICATION

Certification in web development, python prgramming from great learning online platform.

EXTRA CIRRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- 1 KERALA NAVAL NCC cadet
- SCOUT AND GUIDE 2018-2020
- KAYAKING

HOBBIES

- SWIMMIING
- WATICHING ANIMATED MOVIES.

PERSONAL EXPERTIES

- CONFIDENT
- LEARDERSHIP
- CALMNESS
- INNOVATIVE
- ADAPTIVITY

PROJECT

CONFERENCE MANAGMET SYSTEM

ICFOSS

2020-2023

FACULTY MANAGEMENT SYSYTEM

KERALA INFORMATION CENTER

2018-2020

ACHEIVEMENT

- CADET CAPTIAN IN IK NAVAL NCC
- RDC 2021-2022 PARTICIPANT

STUDENT CONCESSION PORTAL

ACADEMIC PROJECT 1

2020-2023